A Register of the S. V. (Sviatoslav Varlaamovich) Denisov Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject file, 1900-1966 and undated.
  - Union des Cosaques (Folder 26: 17)
  - World War, 1914-1918. (Box 27)
    Correspondence, clippings, maps and orders
    - Maps, undated (Folder 27: 1)
    - 2-aia svodnaia kazach'ia diviziia (Folder 27: 2)
    - IV-yi kavaleriiskii korpus (Folder 27: 3)
    - 11-yi Donskoi kazachii polk, 1916-1917 (Folder 27: 4)
- Printed matter, 1918-1939 and undated. (Box 28)
  Appeals, clippings, newspapers, proclamations, arranged chronologically
  - Clippings, 1918-1939 and undated. (Folder 28: 1)
    Includes clippings from Chasovoi (1918), Donskiia viedomosti, Kazach'e slovo, Kubanets, Novoe vremia, Prizyv, Velikaia Rossiia, Vol'naia Kuban', Zaria Rossii
  - Appeals and proclamations, 1919-1920 and undated (Folder 28: 2)
  - "Soobshcheniia shtaba Donskoi armii,", April 1-June 3, 1919 (Folder 28: 3)
- Miscellany, undated (Box 29-33)
  - Clippings from various émigré and Cossack newspapers relating to the Russian Revolution, World War I, Cossack history, religion, and Russian history and culture, duplicates, and notes. Not filmed. Originals retained by Holy Trinity Seminary